[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
You two look like a couple.
Is there something going on?
Oh! I'm sorry.
The path is pretty wide. Did you do that on purpose?
Why did you follow me here?
Did I? I was jogging after practice.
You should apply to be a trainee at the soccer club.
The team really needs extra hands.
The two of us are dating.
Hey.
Why do I have to see you everywhere?
I've been feeling a bit uneasy lately, Jinna. [Go to hell]
Anyway, be careful for now, Anda.
This clearly was sent with bad intentions.
Podduang.
Wake up. You're home.
Yes, baby.
He's really out cold?
Your stir-fried veggies are here, baby.
- Not even going to wait? - What?
Are you going to follow me everywhere or what?
I'm sorry, dear.
I'm not... I'm leaving the elevator.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry, ma'am. - Right.
Right, right. I'm sorry.
Hey, Podduang.
I saw a young man drop you off last night.
So dope. Awesome stuff.
Are you the one who called a ride to the university?
Yes.
Hop on, kiddo.
[Characters, places, and incidents in this production]
[are entirely fictitious.]
[Viewer discretion is advised.]
You did so well, you know?
But don't watch the next scene, Kum.
Why not?
It makes me flustered.
Let's watch it, then?
No, don't.
Totally killed it.
I told you not to watch it.
You're so different from your character in the series.
What?
- Are you jealous? - Nothing.
I know how to make it up to you.
See?
You're teasing this old dog's heart again.
What do you mean?
A short ad break first.
Give me a second.
Ta-da. For you.
- What is it? - Open it.
[Anda]
- Whoa. - Do you like it?
This is lovely.
Notice the number right here.
This is really sweet.
You're my first Andaman.
With this,
how should I reward my good boy?
What's the reward?
Just keep watching the series.
We're about to reach the climax.
- Are we now? - The climax in...
We're about to reach the climax, right?
The tension's rising.
What? That's not what I mean, Kum.
Stop it.
Well, thank you very much, everyone, for making it here today.
I'm really excited that we'll get to watch the ending together.
How do you feel about the series still going so strong right now,
while also trending at number one in both Thailand and neighboring countries?
I'm so delighted.
And thank you for all the support you've given us both.
Is it true that you and Anda are about to release merchandise for fans to collect?
Can you give us a little sneak peek at what it will look like?
I believe our fans will love it.
Here's a hint: you can combine two parts into one.
How sweet!
One more thing. There are only 100 of these, everyone.
If you want to get your hands on one, tonight at 7 p.m.,
click the link on the series' social media pages.
After three series together, when will you two finally make it official?
When should we announce it?
What is this?
Anda?
You don't need to go full incognito like this.
I want to stay by your side.
I miss you, Kum.
Don't give me that smile.
Make sure to get some rest, okay?
I've got you right here, my good source of rest.
Come and let me recharge.
What are you doing?
Nobody will see us.
I hopped in Chai's van and had him drive around the parking lot so many times.
Then I got changed and came here. Rest assured.
Seems like a total hassle, doesn't it?
It does.
That's why I deserve a reward.
What are you doing?
Come on. The windows are tinted. No one can see us.
Kum.
I want to go public.
Is that a good idea, Anda?
This might affect your career.
I'm just done dating you in secret.
I won't have to go full incognito like I've been doing either.
You're gaining popularity, Anda.
You're rising to fame.
I don't think we have to go public.
I'm fine as it is.
But isn't it uncomfortable?
Not being able to be ourselves?
Your family isn't okay with this, are they?
Your father hasn't been in touch with you since you started working on a series.
Hey, Anda.
I'll leave this to you.
I can handle it just fine myself.
You can take your time.
For me, simply being with you is already enough to make me happy.
See?
You're always like this.
How can I not love this old dog?
Kiss me.
Let's hit the road now.
Podduang, are you sure your internet connection is fast enough?
It's slowing down because of Dunk.
- He's glued to his soccer game. - Dunk, turn it off already.
Hey, what the hell? The match is just as important.
Right now, there's nothing as important as the 100 figurines.
You're so right.
30 seconds left.
If I reset the router right now, would you be mad at me?
- Shut up! - Shut it!
Why not make more if you knew it'd sell?
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
[Surfer boy] Seven.
- Six. - Six.
- Five. - Five.
- Four, three. - Four, three.
[Buy It Now] - Two. - Two.
- One. - One.
[Error] [Sorry, the website is temporarily unavailable]
Damn it.
It always happens to me.
What? What's happening? What the fuck happened?
Why are you all quiet? I'm nervous, okay?
[SOLD OUT]
My limited-edition collection is fucking sold out!
I'm so upset, Bum.
No...
Don't touch me!
She's pissed. Better leave her be.
Who the hell is that?
I'm so sad...
Who is it?
What's wrong? You're acting like it's Jinna.
Did you forget about your order? You didn't answer my calls.
Sorry.
Jinna!
You're such a hard worker, delivering food even on your day off.
How many jobs do you have?
He reminds me of Chief Hong from 'Hometown Cha-Cha-Cha.'
I never knew people like this existed.
Come and hang out with us.
I have other work to do.
See you at the soccer club.
Dunk, why are you inviting him in?
This is my place!
Sorry, I was being too friendly.
Hey, come on now.
Let's have dinner.
Yours first.
- What is it? - I don't know.
[Anda Confirms His Relationship with Non-Celebrity Partner!]
Hello, Podduang?
Hello, Bum. Have you seen the news?
I have. I was actually about to call you.
What made you decide to make such a bold move?
I believe the series I've worked on taught me that "love has no bounds."
And I want everyone to know that I stand by the message
that this is who I really am.
I wanted to come on this show first
to remind everyone that we all deserve to love
and be loved in our own way.
Are you worried your popularity might fade after going public?
This has been something I've thought about for a long time.
But I've thought it through. I think it's worth it.
I also believe the fans of the series and the Andaman fandom will understand.
Have you consulted anyone before making the announcement?
I consulted my partner.
Is your partner a celebrity or a non-celebrity?
Non-celebrity.
- A pilot. - A pilot?
What did your family say about this?
I hope they'll understand me.
[#AndaIsNotManly]
[The sausage-fest will rule the world.]
[Coming out takes courage. Why bully them?]
[Mess with my baby, mess with me.]
[I heard he got fucked by a soccer player]
[Your words reflect your upbringing]
[We're so proud of you. #AndaAndHisSmile]
This isn't good.
So many people reposted my tweets. All I see are homophobes.
A lot of the fans are showing him support, though.
There's nothing we can do.
We don't even know how Anda is holding up.
Yeah.
So... How are you and Dunk doing?
Well... It's going alright.
We've gotten used to each other.
It feels like we're more like friends than anything.
It's hard to explain.
Podduang. Honestly,
I'm a little uncomfortable about dating Dunk.
I'm so afraid.
From our first year until now, we know what we're like.
You know what I'm like.
My love life always comes crashing down.
I think this one's on me, really.
It probably won't be the case with Dunk.
Don't know. Don't want to think about it.
You've been his crush since freshman year.
And what about you?
When did he become your crush?
I care about you, Podduang.
I care so much about our group.
Me too.
But as for your relationship, I'm actually okay with it.
Don't worry, Bum.
Your phone's out of juice. Now, you can look up the chords.
Hey, it's okay. I'm leaving soon.
Come on, just take it.
If you rent a portable charger here, you can return it at any station.
Okay.
What's wrong, Podduang?
You don't look okay, Podduang.
It's not about that, Bum.
What? Why am I out of the loop?
It's within the Andaman fandom.
It's about my internship hours with the core team.
I still don't know which team I should join.
I told you to join the soccer team with me. Why complicate things?
No way!
I hate Jinna.
I'll join the basketball team.
It's already full. Where have you been?
- And the volleyball team? - Also full!
- The rugby team doesn't sound so bad. - Full!
- The swimming team? - Also full!
What now? Do I have to be with the chess team?
That team's not full, but it's not on the list.
Though I think the soccer team isn't a bad idea.
Jinna isn't that bad of a guy.
Dunk is on the team, too. I always come to watch him play.
You won't be lonely.
Do you guys notice something?
Whenever we have a problem, we always sit on this damn bench.
Should I just break it?
Nonsense.
[DOT: DREAMS OF TOMORROW]
You almost bumped into me and ran off again.
Is Coach Kong here?
You came.
At this rate, who's actually following whom, I wonder?
I joined the club because my friend is on the team.
I didn't want to see you.
On top of that, it's almost time to submit the document.
I don't want to intern next semester.
I already knew that.
You explained it like something was up.
Why are you getting on my nerves so much?
I'm getting on your nerves?
You're the only one who doesn't like me.
Be honest. Are you mad at me or what?
Or am I making you blush?
Alright, everyone.
This is an intern from the Faculty of Sports and Health Science,
who will assist you this semester.
Give him a round of applause to welcome him.
Take care of him, everyone.
Hey, pick up the pace. Keep it up.
Keep the triangle going.
There, there. That's up, back, and then through.
Podduang.
What is it, Bum?
You seem pretty quiet.
I'm sorry if I'm misunderstanding you,
but I think you're lying to me.
I'm fine, really.
I feel like I'm hurting your feelings.
I'm willing to go back to just being friends with Dunk, Podduang.
If there's something you're not okay with, you can just tell me.
I'm serious.
Bum, calm down and listen to me.
I just used to have a crush on Dunk.
But I'm okay now.
Do you understand where I'm coming from?
I've been disappointed by this kind of thing so many times.
And I don't want to disappoint or have problems with my two best friends.
I've got someone I like now.
I'm sorry?
Well...
We've started seeing each other.
Who is it?
It's Jinna.
Jinna?
Jinna? Which Jinna?
It's that Jinna, alright?
The Jinna.
Damn it...
What did I just tell her?
Please, calm down, honey.
Anda.
Why did you come home so early?
I want to see you, Mom.
Gosh. You know what your dad is like lately.
And what about you?
Are you okay with what I said in the announcement?
You already know how I feel.
I still love you like I always have,
but you need to find some time to talk to your dad.
But I think it's best to wait until he's a bit calmer.
Am I so wrong for being who I am?
And does your brother know about this?
He doesn't.
I hope Itti will understand me.
Everyone's left. Need something?
- Jinna, I... - You like me?
Not that. I don't like you.
And there's no way I would.
Why did you say that, then?
I just...
I just want to make my best friend feel better.
By lying about seeing me?
For what?
Fine. I'm sorry, then.
I didn't mean to tell her that.
I just didn't want to hurt my friend's feelings.
That means...
You and Bum like the same person?
Dunk, is it?
Since I already used your name as an excuse, can you hit on me?
What did you just say?
I know you heard me.
Can you pretend you're hitting on me?
And...
Why would I do that?
You asked me what I was mad at you about.
And?
If you pretend to hit on me, I'll let it go and stop being mad at you.
Please? Just for a month.
I'm only asking for a month.
A month?
Okay.
And that means...?
I'll hit on you.
Do you two realize you've been acting really strange?
Seriously, when did you and Jinna start talking?
Well...
Why? You're worried about your friend?
I don't get it.
I'm confused.
Tell me I'm not dreaming.
What dream?
Fine! I believe now.
You shook me so hard my brain's all upside down.
Well, just in case you're still dreaming.
From now on, I hope you don't mind if I hit on your buddy, okay?
Sure.
No problem.
He's yours.
Dig in.
- So bland. - Yeah, so is my drink.
What? Are you kidding me? Let me have a sip.
Hey, you want my drink, don't you?
Not a chance. I want to drink some Thai tea, too. Let's share.
Podduang!
I got you a bag of cocoa.
When did they start flirting?
My heart's about to stop.
It's okay. I'll call for a rescue team.
[Following]
I think Podduang made the first move.
You're wrong.
From the looks of it, it was definitely Jinna.
Do you know what physiological arousal fucking means?
There's this thing about people who hate each other,
where being in the same room makes their hearts start racing.
They'll break into a sweat, turn red, and get an adrenaline rush.
Podduang is an intern at the soccer club.
He's bound to feel something.
Gosh. You've got it all wrong, Tod.
When it comes to this, it's either the right person or the wrong one.
Podduang hates Jinna's guts.
And you should stop it right now, with those silly theories you read in books.
Jinna.
Who made the first move?
What the hell?
I don't buy it.
How many times do I have to tell you? Jinna really is hitting on me.
Are you really okay with this? You hate his guts.
Well, I... I want to open up to him.
Didn't you two tell me he's not a bad guy?
Jeez... And now you're acting all confused.
Yeah. Believe what he said, Dunk.
Fine. I'm still a bit shocked. I'm sorry.
Nonsense.
So, where are you two at now?
It's not official yet. We're just seeing where things go.
Sheesh...
Is my friend about to get into a relationship?
If that's the case, the rivalry between the two faculties is over.
Now they're two loving faculties.
Stop that now.
When are you going to return my earphones?
What? Come on...
Got flustered, so you changed the subject?
You're getting carried away.
What's wrong, babe?
You called me "babe"? Yuck.
Don't call me that again. I don't like it.
Just kidding.
Yeah, I left them at my place. I'll return them later.
You lost them, didn't you?
Lost? That's ridiculous.
I'll return them soon, Podduang.
Always.
Right. Have you seen Anda at all?
I haven't seen him since the controversy.
But things have gotten a lot better.
People understand him a lot better now.
Yeah. The world has changed a lot. Even I understand him.
Glad things are turning around for him.
I don't want him to stress out.
[I don't know where Anda has gone,
but we, the Andaman fandom, are always right here. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[I love #AndaAndHisSmile so much.]
[The Andaman fandom,
please show him our support. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[Is the #AndaAndHisSmile necessary for a gay person dating someone?]
[None of your business. If you can't think of anything positive,
then shut up. #AndaAndHisSmile]
[People leaving rude comments are just jealous.]
[Did no one ever love them? #AndaAndHisSmile]
[Bum: I'm so happy our hashtag has reached number one on the trending list]
[Podduang: Muah, muah]
On this episode of 'Woody Talk, ' we're with Anda,
a renowned actor who's at the center of attention right now.
What would make you go public? How do you feel?
Are you a fan of Anda?
Oh, yes.
Same, actually.
I also love the Andaman fandom.
To respect yourself and others,
- Can I watch this with you? - No problem.
What made you decide to make such a bold move?
- He's adorable, isn't he? - He really is.
How long have you been his fan?
About two or three years. What about you?
Same for me, actually. About that long, too.
But it's a shame he's been getting so much hate lately.
These toxic netizens who just keep hating are out of their minds, aren't they?
- Yeah. - I feel so bad for him.
You didn't press the button?
I got distracted.
- Anda is just too adorable. - I'm sorry.
Perfect timing.
He's cute, isn't he?
And when Anda acted with James...
Look, this beach scene is just so great.
I saved this one too.
- Really? - It's such a beautiful scene.
This is my room.
We're basically neighbors.
Hey! Are you kidding me?
But we've never seen each other before, have we?
You're right. What a coincidence.
Right. My name is Amp.
If you have any problems, feel free to knock on my door.
My name is Podduang. You can also simply call me "Pod."
Okay. See you.
Right. Bye-bye.
[JINNA] [Hello]
It's hard to live as a celebrity, isn't it?
Even admitting who you like feels like a crime.
Are you okay?
I heard you had it rough.
I was too scared to message you.
I was afraid you weren't ready to open up.
It was brutal, actually.
Why is it so hard to be myself?
Because our lives don't simply depend on us, Anda.
You're right.
Ever since I made the announcement,
I feel like I'm completely lost.
So lost that sometimes I ask myself
if I've actually slipped up.
My company even warned me.
Even worse,
my manager told me that...
all the upcoming series we were supposed to shoot
have been put on hold.
On top of that, someone sent me that freaky doll, too.
Do that many people really hate me, Jinna?
I'm so tired, Jinna.
I'm so tired.
Then come back to us.
I've known you for three years,
and you're certainly loved by so many more people.
I don't mean to get all emotional,
but like...
I've gotten to know so many people since I started working as an actor.
But you three are the only ones
I can really talk to you about everything.
Right.
Art, Tod, and I are always here.
Everything is just piling up on me and I have no idea where to even start.
My family wasn't okay with my announcement either.
They haven't been okay with me being an actor from day one.
Anda.
Someday, your family will appreciate your effort.
One step at a time, okay?
Anda.
You're looking really run-down these days.
Don't forget to make some time to rest.
I'm worried about you.
So are Tod and Art.
Thank you.
It's okay, it's okay.
- What class do you have today, Jinna? - Hey.
- Professor Bankpan is so strict. - I'm done.
I don't want to study with him at all.
He really is.
That's Podduang and Bum.
- I'll be right back. - I wonder who he's seeing.
Showing his true colors already.
Hello.
Hello to whom?
Me?
Or that girl?
What? Jealous?
I'm here too, you know?
What's with all the sweet talk?
- You didn't reply to my DMs. - I'd already fallen asleep.
This is Risa, a scholarship student in Accounting.
We go back to freshman year.
Hello, Podduang and Bum.
I'm Risa. Nice to meet you all.
Right. I have a class to attend.
We're running late, too.
- Let's go. - Hey, hold on.
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
Hurry. We're late.
They all seem very friendly.
Well, isn't that nice?
Who would want to be like you anyway?
[Faculty of Engineering]
Should we have steak at our usual place?
Anda is here after all.
- Let's go. - I'm in.
But I think...
Anda probably wants to go to our favorite shabu-shabu place, right?
That's a good idea.
- Art. - What?
Do you really have to oppose everything I say?
Come on. It's called "presenting an option."
I'm fine with anything, actually.
But shabu-shabu might be a better choice?
- Steak is better. - Shabu-shabu.
- Steak. - Shabu-shabu.
Steak.
- I've got it. - Shabu-shabu.
Shabu-shabu?
A pad kaphrao place near campus.
- Oh... - Oh, come on.
Seriously?
Come on, let's go.
Anda.
We need to talk.
Hey, wait a minute.
Who are you?
We need to talk, just the two of us.
Just talk about it here.
Why do you need to talk to him alone?
Just tell us.
Can you stay the fuck away?
Art, calm down.
- Let me talk. - Calm down, calm down.
Listen to him. Let's not make any sudden moves.
Wait and see.
Why are you so fucking selfish, Anda?
Why did you have to ruin someone else's life too?
Do you know the company didn't just put your series on hold?
This affects me, too.
We're the lead partners.
Why did you have to ruin my life as well?
James, I'm deeply sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry for fucking what?
Back then, I liked you because I really did.
When you rejected me,
I respected your choice, but I never mixed this shit with work!
I didn't do it because I was uncomfortable with you.
I just didn't want to pretend and keep lying to people. That's all!
What about our partner projects?
You can't just be whoever the fuck you want to be.
Aren't you being too selfish, Anda?
With this kind of stuff, there are seniors and businesses tied to it.
I just want you and me to make the most of it.
Once it's over, you can flirt with or sleep with whoever you want!
James, calm down!
Are you that thirsty for a sexual partner?
I never knew you'd be like this.
- And so fucking what, Anda? - Hey!
Seems like you've got a problem.
Hey, you.
I hope you don't do something stupid on our turf,
with our tools and our friends around.
Leave now if you don't want to make the headlines.
You... All of you better get used to fucking dealing with me.
Hey.
Hey, listen to me.
- Hey! - Hands off!
Leave already.
- I don't want to see you anymore. - No.
I'm here because I want to hear you say that you hate me.
Yes.
Tell him, "I hate you!"
- Please listen to me. - No!
- Hey. - I hate you.
I hate you! Are you satisfied now?
I really am!
But I didn't order anything.
I've got this for you. I think you'll like it.
What is it?
Open it. I want to see your reactions.
I only asked you to pretend to flirt with me, you know?
You don't have to go this far.
Where did you get this?
Hey, Anda.
I need your help.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
I have to go now.
Hey. This is your room.
Bye-bye.
[Mentioned you in their story. So cute!] [Add to your story]
Jinna.
I really like you.
What the hell? That came out of nowhere.
You know how hot Jinna is, right?
I only want you to pretend to hit on me. Don't get too attached.
I don't like pretending, though.
You've been practicing hard today, so I got you some water.
For me?
This award is for you all.
[Team Anda]
You're standing here arguing with me nonstop,
and you actually expect me to be proud of your stupid award?
Will there be a day when my dad accepts me?
At the end of the day, I feel like I can never truly be myself
as long as I'm still alive.
I just want to tell you that if you're hurting, just let it out.
Don't worry about how people will see you.